I do not know how many houses there are in Norrland, which many do not know that it haunts.
The house in Yrttivaara was definitely such a house we did not know, but which we soon became aware that paranormal things happen in.
The house was built during the Second World War and part of the house was then a store, where they sold nails.
At that time, you had to buy a whole railway carriage with nails, which you also did.
The deal was closed down and demolished, but remaining the old wooden stairs and the concrete slab, where the store once stood.
The house changed owners and renovations began.
That's when everything started.
I shudder when I stand here.
Strange.
I think this is current to the machine.
So there we have nothing.
I got the feeling when I came in here, that I was not welcome to be there.
Like "out of here!"
Yes, it's a bit like that.
*Footsteps*
Was that a step up from?
You, I forgot to say one thing.
When I was standing here before and just going out, I thought I heard like a growl.
It is also interesting, they have plans for this house.
They are renovating and that is when it has started.
Do you know what they have for plan with this house?
I haven't been rugged here before.
I have been in here and fixed stuff.
The forest.
I also asked if this ditch they have dug out.
I wondered when they did that.
There is memory out there.
So what they have dug is next to a cat that they have buried.
One of the people who have lived here said we have to move on the cat and someone said "No, we shit in the cat"
And I also think, you pull a deep sheep out in the woods, when you have to dig down a cable.
It is open now.
You think so.
There was a lot that came here right away.
I'll check if you have electromagnetic fields at you.
As you can see, it's zero.
At Tony here.
Try walking towards the doors.
The camera is further in.
Lennie does Lennie hear us now?
Yes.
Where is the fog?
The fog came where you stand now, then it passed the stairs two, three steps down, thick.
Okay, I get 37 years here too.
Ugh what shivers it was here.
Are you down here all?
You see that it is moisture damage, it drops in.
Cables that were loose.
*First words from Polterscript when we enter the basement*
How disgusting that was.
At first I thought I was bitten by something, but there is nothing here.
That was like a shock in your finger.
Like I take in two cables that have low power, I felt it was tingling.
Irritated?
You, the owner said it started to tingle in the body.
It was interesting that you feel it.
And now 4 degrees again.
4.5.
It went up to 7 degrees and this one went.
Warmer.
Nothing.
It was steps.
But it came .. There is nothing up there.
I just shudder.
Tap the wall again if it was you.
The knocks were great.
Do it again.
If the lady is here, come in here to us.
What a stinging feeling in my head I got.
I can stand out there, I'm in front of a camera if I'm out there.
Do you stand Johan?
If you stand there.
Now we are divided, Niclas is behind here.
Make that sound again.
Join us on some tearmark now that Niclas.